https://www.carerssupport.org.uk/about-us/our-policies-and-procedures/

Our policies and procedures
Our vision, values and strategic aims have been shaped by the experiences of local carers.
We actively seek feedback on the quality and delivery of our services and the impact these services have on carer’s lives.
The plans, policies and procedures that support our aims can be viewed on this page.
Strategic Plan
Our vision, values and strategic aims have been shaped by the experiences of local carers. Their views and feedback combined with the knowledge and understanding of our staff, volunteers, managers and Trustees have helped shape our Strategic Plan for 2015 – 2020.
Carers Support West Sussex Strategic Plan 2015-2020
Strategic Plan - Appendix One
Strategic Plan - Appendix Two
Strategic Plan - Appendix Three
Strategic Plan - Appendix Four
Strategic Plan - Appendix Five
2017/18 Impact Report
Compliments and Complaints
Feedback is vital to make sure we are providing a quality service to carers.
Our teams welcome your comments and suggestions and take every opportunity to continuously improve our standards across all services for carers.
If you are a carer or colleague, please do pass on any feedback you wish us to take into account and feel free to raise any concern or complaint.
You will be assured of a carer-friendly response.
We consider it very important that carers and others can be part of any process to resolve difficulties. Our staff will do their best to ensure you are regularly updated on progress of any investigation and are informed of the outcome within a realistic timescale.
Compliments and Complaints Procedure
Carers Support West Sussex Printable Feedback Form
Online Community House Rules
Privacy Policy
Equality, Diversity and Inclusion
Carers Support West Sussex values diversity and recognise that people with different backgrounds, skills, attitudes and experiences enrich the communities we serve contributing fresh ideas, valuable insights and new perceptions to the way our organisation works either as carers, staff or partners.
Our aim is to be an inclusive organisation that promotes a culture that values differences where diversity is fully embraced and respected.
We are committed to challenging all forms of discrimination or disadvantage and aim to ensure that no individual or group is directly or indirectly discriminated against for any reason with regard to employment or access to services.
Positive about Disabled People
Carers Support have gained Positive About Disabled People accreditation and have been given permission by Jobcentre Plus to use the Two Ticks symbol, having made the following
5 commitments:
to interview all disabled applicants who meet the minimum criteria for a job vacancy and to consider them on their abilities
to discuss with disabled employees, at any time but at least once a year, what you can both do to make sure they can develop and use their abilities
to make every effort when employees become disabled to make sure they stay in employment
to take action to ensure that all employees develop the appropriate level of disability awareness needed to make these commitments work
to review these commitments every year and assess what has been achieved, plan ways to improve on them and let employees and Job Centre Plus know about progress and future plans
Equality and Diversity Policy
Carer Engagement Policy
Privacy Policy
Carers Support West Sussex respects the privacy of visitors to our website and wants to protect any personal information that you give to us.
This statement is made in order to comply with the provisions of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), and to tell you how Carers Support West Sussex will use any personal information that you give to us.
Carers Support West Sussex is registered as a data controller with the Information Commissioner for the United Kingdom.
To contact our Data Protection Officer, please email dpo@carerssupport.org.uk or, to speak with our Data Protection officer, please call 0300 028 8888.
Privacy Policy
Subject Access Request Protocol
Data Protection Privacy Notice - Recruitment
Volunteer Privacy Policy
